mathportal.org 2019-05-10

# Privacy Policy for www.mathportal.org

This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by mathportal.org, how it is used and safeguard your information. 

### Log Files 

We collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), the browser you used to visit our site, the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded, used to improve the content of our Web page 

### Cookies and Web Beacons 

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. 

We also use third party advertisements on mathportal.org to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. 

###  DoubleClick DART cookies 

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history. DART uses "non personally identifiable information". It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx 

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. 

### Email Address

We collect the e-mail addresses of visitors those who post messages to our guest book or suggestion board. We are not sharing any of those email addresses to any third party. 

### External Links

By visiting the external links shown in Link page of this site, visitors are stipulated with the Privacy Policy and Terms of Services of respective web sites they visits. 

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at office@mathportal.org.
